citibank.ae 2006-06-16

# Citi - Privacy

|  **Citigroup Privacy Promise for Consumers**

While information is the cornerstone of our ability to provide superior service, our most important asset is our customers' trust. Keeping customer information secure, and using it only as our customers would want us to, is a top priority for all of us at Citibank as a member of the Citigroup family of companies. Here then, is our promise to our individual customers: 

  1. We will safeguard, according to strict standards of security and confidentiality, any information our customers share with us. 
  2. We will limit the collection and use of customer information to the minimum we require to deliver superior service to our customers, which includes advising our customers about our products, services and other opportunities, and to administer our business. 
  3. We will permit only authorized employees, who are trained in the proper handling of customer information, to have access to that information. Employees who violate our Privacy Promise will be subject to our normal disciplinary process. 
  4. We will not reveal customer information to any external organization unless we have previously informed the customer in disclosures or agreements, been authorized by the customer, or are required by law. 
  5. We will always maintain control over the confidentiality of our customer information. We may, however, facilitate relevant offers from reputable companies. These companies are not permitted to retain any customer information unless the customer has specifically expressed interest in their products or services. 
  6. We will tell customers in plain language initially, and at least once annually, how they may remove their names from marketing lists. At any time, customers can contact us to remove their names from such lists. 
  7. Whenever we hire other organizations to provide support services, we will require them to conform to our policy standards and to allow us to audit them for compliance. 
  8. For purposes of credit reporting, verification and risk management, we will exchange information about our customers with reputable reference sources and clearinghouse services. 
  9. We will not use or share - internally or externally - personally identifiable medical information for any purpose other than the underwriting or administration of a customer's policy, claim or account, or as disclosed to the customer when the information is collected, or to which the customer consents. 
  10. We will attempt to keep customer files complete, up to date, and accurate. We will tell our customers how and where to conveniently access their account information (except when we're prohibited by law), and how to notify us about errors which we will promptly correct. 

We will continuously assess ourselves to ensure that customer privacy is respected. We will conduct our business in a manner that fulfills our promise in the many nations in which we do business. 

**Internet Privacy Policy**

We want you to understand what personally identifiable information ("Information") that is collected through a web site operated by Citibank* ("we" or "us") and how it may later be disclosed. 

You can visit a web site and find out about Citibank products and services and use value-added services that may be available without giving us any Information about yourself. If you must register at a web site to use one of its features or are interested being contacted by Citibank about its products and/or services, you may input Information about yourself at the web site. Where available, you may update your contact Information online. Otherwise, you will need to contact Citibank at the telephone number provide in order to do so. Any Information you provide to us will be handled in accordance with the "Citigroup Privacy Promise for Consumers." 

Non-customers who receive promotional e-mail messages about Citibank products and services may elect to not receive ('opt out' of) further messages. If you opt out from receiving these e-mail messages, we will retain your e-mail address solely for the purposes of honoring your request. 

In order to provide better service, we may use "cookies", which may be set by us or by another company for us. A cookie is a small piece of information that a web site stores on your web browser that can later be retrieved and read only by the same site. We use cookies for a administrative purposes and to enhance your online experience. For example, we may use cookies to track the number of visitors to our site or to enable us present rotating information to you at our site. You can set up your web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies from being set. 

Citibank collects Information about customers through the applications it receives and from other sources. If you are a customer, additional details about the Information we collect and how it may be disclosed is contained in **Our Privacy Notice** , which is provided to you at account opening. 

If you wish to review Information provided on online applications, you can contact us to request a copy of the personal account information you provided through our customer service numbers. There may be a charge for certain Information that is requested. It may also be possible for Customers to review and change contact information such as address, phone and e-mail information by signing on and updating their personal profile. To protect your privacy, proof of identity or other authentication is required any time you contact us. 

The Information we collect about you comes from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as your name, address, and telephone number, 
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or non-affiliated third parties, such as your account balances, payment history, and account activity, 
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency such as your credit bureau reports and other information relating to your creditworthiness, and 
  * Information we receive about you from other sources, such as your employer and other third parties. 

Citibank may share Information with several types of entities, including other affiliates among the family of companies controlled by Citigroup Inc, as well as non-affiliated third parties, as described below. 
  * Our affiliates are the family of companies controlled by Citigroup. Affiliates to whom we may disclose personal information about you are in several different businesses, including banking, credit cards, consumer finance, insurance and securities. Our affiliates include those doing business under the names CitiFinancial, CitiMortgage, Smith Barney, and Primerica. 
  * Non-affiliated third parties are those not part of the family of companies controlled by Citigroup. We may disclose personal information about you to the following types of non-affiliated third parties: (1) Financial services providers, such as companies engaged in banking, credit cards, consumer finance, securities, and insurance, and (2) Non-financial companies, such as companies engaged in direct marketing and the selling of consumer products and services. 

In response to a Vermont regulation, we will automatically treat accounts with Vermont billing addresses as having instructed us to limit the sharing of Information with non-affiliated third parties. If we disclose Information about you to non-affiliated third parties with whom we have joint marketing agreements, we will only disclose your name, address, other contact information, and information about our transactions or experiences with you. 

In response to a California law, effective July 1, 2004, we will automatically treat accounts with California mailing addresses as having instructed us not to disclose Information about you to non-affiliated third parties, except as permitted by applicable California law. 

From time to time, we may change this Internet Privacy Policy. The effective date of this policy, as stated below, indicates the last time this policy was revised or materially changed. Checking the effective date below allows you to determine whether there have been changes since the last time you reviewed the policy. 

Effective Date: This policy was last modified on July 1, 2004

* All references to Citibank mean Citibank, N.A., Citibank, F.S.B., Citibank (West), FSB or Citibank Texas, N.A., the bank that maintains your account relationship in the United States. 

|
